Hmm?
Mindless violence
lit up the sky.
America-- the 1970s.
The energy crisis is real.
♪ I'm runnin' away
- A time of unrest and mistrust.
- I have never been a quitter.
- It was a night of terror.
- A time of fear and violence.
We are entering a satanic age!
Anyone who can't see that
is blind!
Television documents the chaos,
beams the horror
into our living room.
And so it is done.
But it also offers comfort.
April 4, 1971--
the first episode of UBC's
"Night Owls" goes to air.
The network's hopes
for a late-night hit
are riding on
the shoulders of the host,
a popular Chicago
radio announcer.
Good evening, night owls.
I'm your host, Jack Delroy.
And thank you for allowing me
into your living rooms
for the first of what I hope
will be many, many shows.
I'd like to thank everyone who
helped bring this dream to life,
especially my dear mom and dad
back in Berwyn, Illinois,
who I know are sitting
in front of their TV set,
big smiles on their faces,
watching "The Tonight Show"
with Johnny Carson.
With its entertaining
mix of interviews,
music, and sketch comedy,
"Night Owls" with Jack Delroy
captures the hearts
and minds of midnight America.
Well, I am sick of it, Crog,
stuck in the cave all day,
cooking your sabertooth stew.
Oi, fellas,
does this sound familiar?
This is an Amazonian
bird-eating spider.
Looks like your furry
little friend, uh,
might have gotten
a better offer.
- Don't panic. I got it, Jack.
I got it. Excuse me, sir.
- Gus.
Five nights a week,
Jack helps an anxious nation
forget its troubles.
In November 1972,
Jack inks a five-year deal
with UBC owner Walker Bedford.
Welcome to UBC family, Jack.
What did you have to sacrifice
to get here tonight?
With an Emmy nomination
to his name
and growing audience share,
Jack sights are set
on the coveted late-night crown.
By Jack's side through
everything is his wife,
the beloved stage actress
Madeleine Piper.
Despite Jack's relentless
quest to be number one,
they are considered
one of showbiz's happiest
and most enduring couples.
Madeleine is his muse
and his confidante,
but she is not
his only source of support.
Jack's association
with The Grove,
a men-only club located
in the redwoods of California,
has been the subject of rumors
since his days in radio.
Established in the 1800s
and counting
among its members politicians,
entertainers,
and captains of industry,
The Grove has long
portrayed itself
as a harmless summer camp
for the rich and powerful.
But speculation swirls around
its taste for arcane ceremony
and its power to make
and break careers.
...8...7...6...
Four seasons on, and ratings
still fail to match Carson.
The nominations mount,
but no trophy.
Jack's reputation as perennial
also-ran starts to bite.
He knows that history
remembers only kings.
Then, in September 1976,
Jack's world is
turned upside-down
when Madeleine, a nonsmoker,
is diagnosed
with terminal lung cancer.
In October, Madeleine makes a
special appearance on the show.
Jack and I first met
when I was doing
"Oh! Calcutta!"...
- Oh, God.
- ...at the Eden.
My, you should have
seen him blush
when he came backstage
and [ Gasps ] was
confronted with all those
glorious naked bodies.
Remember, darling?
Madeleine, I don't think
we need to talk about...
See, [Gasps] he's blushing
right now.
How is a girl
not supposed to fall
in love with that?
Isn't she something,
ladies and gentlemen?
- It is the highest-rating
episode in "Night Owls" history,
but still falls
a point short of Carson.
- I love you, Jack.
Two weeks later,
Madeleine is dead.
A grieving Jack
shuns the media.
He flees New York,
his location unknown.
Just one month later,
and to the surprise of many,
UBC announces his return.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. Jack Delroy.
But the gap between Delroy
and Carson continues to widen.
Jack and his longtime producer,
Leo Fiske,
go out of their way
to court controversy,
in a bid
to improve audience share.
You used to be
the [bleep] man, Jack.
What the
happened to you?
Huh?
We are gonna take a break,
and I'll--
I'll be right back.
And you will not.
Where the [bleep] do you think
you're going? Huh?
- Open the [bleep] door!
- Ratings are in free fall.
Sponsors are nervous.
Jack's contract
is set to expire.
Everything is on the line
when Sweeps Week begins
on Halloween night, 1977.
A desperate Jack plans
an episode
he hopes will turn
his fortunes around.
Get the audience in, guys.
What you are about to see is
the recently discovered
master tape of what went
to air that night,
as well as previously unreleased
behind-the-scenes footage.
It is the live TV event
that shocked a nation--
"Late Night With the Devil."
Tonight's broadcast
is brought to you
by the Cavendish Group
of Companies.
Let's shake on it.
Live from UBC Studios
in New York City,
it's "Night Owls"
with Jack Delroy!
Joining us on our
spooky Halloween special,
Christou...
Carmichael Haig...
Dr. June Ross-Mitchell with
the subject of her new book,
Lilly...
Miss Cleo James with
a bewitching jazz medley...
plus our annual
Halloween costume parade.
But now here's Mr. Midnight--
Jack Delroy!
Oh, boy. Jack?
Where the hell is he?
Uh, Jack, you're on.
Leo, he's not, uh...
- Boo!
Aw, Jesus, Mary, and Joseph!
Gus McConnell,
ladies and gentlemen.
You.
Oh, good evening, night owls,
and thank you for allowing me
into your living rooms
once again.
We've got an incredible show
lined up for you tonight
as we celebrate all of
the fiendish fun of Halloween.
Ew. Oh, hello.
Um, what do you got there, Gus?
A theremin Jack.
It's a musical instrument.
Oh, that's not music, Gus.
That is actually
the sound you get
when you're tuning
your car radio,
searching for music.
What's interesting about
a theremin, Jack,
is you play it
without touching it.
So, you're not meant
to touch it?
No, sir. No touching.
Why, Gus, if only you'd shown
the same restraint
at the Melody Burlesque
after Friday's show.
Hmm.
Think we should raise the bar
in here
a little bit tonight, folks.
Um, anybody go
to the Yankees' parade?
Yeah! Any Reggie Jackson
fans in here?
Knew she was.
Now, there's a rumor
going around
that "Cosmo" magazine
has approached Reggie to be
their very own Mr. October.
- Ooh.
We can expect Reggie's
impressive homerun spree
to continue well
into the offseason.
We doing good?
Have one more?
Hey! Whoa!
That one went
over the fence.
Whew!
- I don't get that joke, Jack.
- Oh, well.
I guess we're gonna have
to raise the bar
to Gus's standards now, folks.
Uh, yeah, so, apparently,
President Jimmy Carter...
Really, Leo?
Oh, you're-- Oh, well, okay.
Easy pickings, I guess.
Um...
so, President Carter
held a press conference today
announcing a reorganization
of his staff.
When asked if his brother Billy
was part of the plans,
the president said
that he'd offered
Billy a chance
to head either the FBI--
is this true?-- or the CIA.
Wow.
- That can't be true.
- Apparently, Billy said
he refused to head any agency
that he couldn't spell.
- I get that joke.
- You got it?
- I got it.
- Gus got it.
Well, night owls,
we've got a heck of a show
in store for you tonight,
and I'm very excited for you
to see it all unfold
before your very eyes.
I really hope you love it.
Gosh, I hope you love it.
Please love it,
because, well...
it's Sweeps Week.
Oh! That's right.
Where is Vincent Price
when you need him?
Boy, I tell you what.
Now, Sweeps Week,
as we all know,
is the all-important
national ratings period.
But, hey, do I look nervous
to you, Gus?
You better believe it, Jack.
We all know how important
it is to keep our sponsors
and affiliates happy.
But in my humble opinion,
there is only one person
who really matters
in this whole darn
crazy business.
- Well, thank you Jack.
- And that is you, our viewer.
You have stood by me
through thick and thin,
good times and bad.
Especially the bad.
It was your support
that [Sighs] brought me back
into this very studio
a year ago,
when I could have
easily thrown in the towel,
when many suggested
that I should have
thrown in the towel.
This show is-- and
it always has been-- for you.
- Love you, Jack!
- And [Sighs]...
Leo, can we please get that
woman a Nielsen viewing diary?
Come on.
Thank you all.
What do you say, night owls?
On with the show, huh?
Yeah!
- Alright
Interest in the occult has seen
a major revival in recent years.
This is true.
You open any newspaper today,
you're gonna see
hundreds of ads for psychics
or fortune tellers,
exorcists, even.
Whoa!
Now, as you know,
here on "Night Owls,"
we think it's very important
to keep an open mind.
Our first guest tonight--
I am so excited
about this young man--
is a shining light
in this movement.
Some call him a medium;
others, a spiritualist.
Some have even called him
a miracle worker.
We know him by one name,
and, well,
that's probably because one name
is all he seems to have.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please help me welcome
the mysterious,
the mononymous Christou.
Thank you for being here.
So, it is just Christou,
is that right?
Sí, that is correct.
Thank you for inviting me
onto your program.
Oh, please, thank you
for taking time
out of your
busy touring schedule.
You are a hot ticket these days.
I tell you what.
- It is my pleasure.
- Now, as I understand it,
a night like tonight,
a spooky night like Halloween,
holds a special significance
for someone in your profession.
That is correct.
All Hallows Eve is a time
to break open the doors
to the underworld.
It is the last chance for the
spirits of the recently deceased
to attend
to any unfinished business.
- Hmm.
- Ooh.
So that explains
the significance, then,
of the Halloween masks.
- Sí, yes.
We use them to hide
from the angry spirits.
Oh. I'm so curious.
Do you hear these voices of
the dead all the time?
The energy is ever-present, sí.
And then I guess
the burning question is,
how the hell
do you get any sleep?
I mean, right?
Just think of my mind
like the ham radio,
picking up frequencies
in the airwaves.
When I no longer want to listen,
I simply switch it off.
Just like that? Wow.
Okay, well, then I think it is
time, ladies and gentlemen,
that we fire up
those frequencies.
The energy in here
is very strong.
Thank you, Phil.
The floor is yours, sir.
Ladies and gentlemen, Christou.
I'm already receiving
some signals here.
The letter "P," I'm hearing.
Peter.
Pete.
No, wait.
It's clearer now.
Peterson.
I'm hearing the name Peterson.
- Peterman?
- What? I'm sorry.
Sir, you're up there. Yeah.
Okay, okay, sir. sir.
You can stand up back there.
Thank you.
Hi, Mr. Peterson.
- Uh, no.
Uh, my wife's maiden name
was Peterman.
Yes, that is it-- Peterman.
She's in the room with us now.
She is?
Your wife has crossed over,
sí?
You could say that.
She ran off with my neighbor
five years ago.
- Sorry to hear that.
- Oh, don't be.
My golf game's
never been better.
No, but there is a--
Now I'm hearing
the name Elizabeth.
No, her name was Helen.
- There was no Beth or Betty?
- Correct.
- There was a Betty.
- No. You're correct.
There was no Beth or Betty.
- A name starting with "B."
- Oh, my name's Barry.
- That's not it.
- No, it has been for 42 years.
Gone. The spirit has passed.
I'm sorry.
Sometimes the signal
gets scrambled.
Studio lights, cameras.
I am only a messenger.
I concentrate.
Barry, have a seat.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- And you, sir?
Looks like you went
on a shopping spree with Gus
down at, uh, Barney's
Discount Costume Warehouse, huh?
Got quite a steal on that, huh?
Don't be upset.
I'm just ribbing you.
- Oh, Jack.
I'm receiving something.
I'm getting a--
Oh, yes, this intrigues.
Good evening, ladies.
- Good evening.
Evening, evening.
- Who is Edward?
Eddie? He was a son or brother
for one of you, sí?
Edmond was my little brother.
- And you were the mother, sí?
- Sí. I mean, yes.
Deduction, Jack,
not psychic powers.
I am still impressed. Wow.
Something bad happened
to Edmond.
It's... hard to talk about it?
Yes.
- Many questions remain.
- Well, h-he--
It may be that Edmond
took his own life?
Quite recently, too.
- Five years ago.
I know, but it feels
like only yesterday.
Such a terrible tragedy.
There was much confusion
why he did this, no?
Terrible sadness and confusion.
This is so.
- There was no note. Nothing.
- No.
He was such a happy boy.
None of us knew
he was in so much pain.
Eddie wants you to know
that he is at peace now.
He's sorry for the suffering
he has caused.
He communicates this to you.
His heart is full of love.
Now I'm hitting
the word "papa."
Well, Dad was always Dad.
We never--
No, wait. Um...
When Edmond was little,
he had a teddy named Papa.
- This is true.
- Oh, my God. I remember.
I kept all his things.
Can you please tell him
that Papa is safe?
I do not need to tell him this.
He already knows.
Thank you.
You are both so beautiful.
Bless you.
Bless you all!
- Wow!
Wow! What a-- What a gift.
Thank you.
Christou! Wow!
Now these tour dates
should be showing up
on your screens momentarily.
We're gonna have to
take a quick break, folks.
When we come back, though,
one of the old friends
of our show who always...
- Christou?
Something very intense here.
Perhaps-- Are we getting
another message from Edmond?
No, no. This is...
I'm getting the name... Minnie.
Does anyone here know a Minnie?
Please accept.
Does this name mean anything
to anyone in the studio?
No? Um, perhaps a name
that sounds like Minnie.
Maybe it's like a Millie
or a Mandy.
- I had a Great-Aunt Molly.
- It's Minnie!
Please! Who will accept?
So much sadness.
I see [Gasps] a wedding ring.
An unmarried man
with a wedding ring.
The spirit needs to talk to you.
Who are you?!
It's okay, folks, it's just our
old par cans acting up.
Gone. S-She's gone.
S-S-She's gone.
- Leo?
We're gonna take
a quick break,
and we're gonna be
right back after these messages.
And we're clear.
Gus to wardrobe.
Hey, Mr. Christou,
that was fantastic.
You are truly blessed.
Jack, can we talk?
- Not right now, Gus.
- It's just backstage.
They're saying you and Leo
have got something cooked up
when that girl comes on.
- As far as I know,
we're sticking to the rundown.
- Right, right.
It's just, I saw restraints,
Jack, and-- and knives.
I've got to be honest with you.
We're a little spooked
back there.
What the hell
are you still doing here?
Get to wardrobe, pronto.
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
- Fantastic segment, fellas.
- Mr. Christou,
you look like you
might need a bourbon.
- Just some water, please.
- In this place?
I'll see what I can do.
- Some water for Mr. Christou.
Are you happy to stay with us
a little longer?
I really should be--
- That's the spirit.
I can't wait to catch your act,
by the way.
Here, you've got some blood
under your nose.
Jack, mind if we...
- Thank you.
Jesus Christ.
The charlatan really
went all-out there.
Oh, boy. That bit with the
lights was your idea, wasn't it?
If you liked it, yeah,
I'll take full credit.
- Mm-hmm.
- What did you think
about our friend Barry?
You okay, buddy?
- Yeah. Just that last--
Look, whatever happened
was great television.
Don't let it rattle you.
Okay, some orders of business.
We're running long,
late to break.
Okay, but we're not
bumping Cleo again.
Well, we'll try
to make up some time.
Oh, don't look now,
but Cavendish's new
vice president of marketing
and his wife
are sitting in the front row
with the head of airtime.
You're looking directly at them.
I don't understand that.
Hey, they want to talk to you.
They want to meet you.
No, I don't have time to play
kiss-ass right now.
In case you hadn't noticed,
I'm trying to host
a nationally syndicated
talk show.
And I'm trying to help you
keep it on the air.
- McConnell?
- Okay.
- Where's McConnell?
- Next break.
- Mm.
- Okay?
How's June? Did they land?
Is she okay?
- She's fine. Just fine.
- Great. The girl?
Jack, will you please relax?
Everything's going very,
very well.
Phil, what the hell's
going on with those lights?
- We're working on it.
- 30 seconds, people!
- Hey.
- Nothing's been fixed
since 1956.
- Hey, great show so far.
- Sammy, how are you?
- Good. How are you?
I'm okay.
How's my hair looking?
- Alright. You look great.
- Good.
Bats in the cave?
- You're all clear.
Thank you.
- Hey, Jack, which card?
- Hey.
- Is this necessary?
You got a little bit
of a sweat going on, honey.
Please, stop!
Fine. Suit yourself.
Hey. Hmm?
Fear not, friends, your humble
sidekick has returned.
- Stand by everyone.
- Staging, the door.
- Too kind.
Haig's on next.
Pay him no mind.
He's all wax, no wick.
Okay?
And we're back in 5...4...
Thank you. Welcome back
to our Halloween special, folks.
For those of you just tuning in,
Mr. Christou here wowed us
before the break
with a demonstration
of his mediumistic powers.
It was really something.
Am I right?
Amazing.
Our next guest
is someone equally renowned
in his own field.
Once known to us all
as Carmichael the Conjurer.
You remember him? Yeah?
Well, he hung up the wand
several years ago to become
one of the leading voices of
the skeptics movement.
Ladies and gentlemen,
make welcome,
if you dare,
Mr. Carmichael Haig.
So good to see you again, Car.
It's wonderful to be here,
Jack.
Mind if I smoke?
Please be my guest.
Oh, boy, that was good.
Mmm.
Wow.
He's still got it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Holy smoke.
Come-- Come on.
I'm right here.
Car...
we all know you
from the Vegas shows,
the TV specials.
Your group-hypnosis routine
was the first of its kind.
Absolutely boggled my mind
when I saw it.
Many regarded you
as the best in the biz.
And I know my saying
that won't embarrass you.
Correct. On all counts.
Continue, dear friend.
- But in recent years,
it seems
you've turned your attention
to something a little more,
shall we say, philanthropic?
- You mean IFSIP?
- IFSIP.
Now, IFSIP, for those of you
not in the know, is an acronym.
It stands for-- let me
get this right here--
the International Federation
of Scientific Investigation
into the Paranormal.
Ooh. It's a lot of words.
We've got some pictures up
right here.
Take a look.
Photogenic lot, aren't we?
Yes, it is our mission
to test these claims
and determine
what is trickery
and what may, in fact,
be genuine psi phenomena.
Oh, that's me about to embark
on a little ghost hunt
in Amityville.
My dear friends Ed
and Lorraine Warren
declined the invitation
to join me.
Easily spooked.
Car, be honest with me.
What is the harm
for those of us who just want to
believe in something mysterious,
something bigger than ourselves, hmm?
Jack, I'm the first to admit
that the world would be
a more interesting place
if, uh-- if people
could magically bend spoons
or divine water with a stick
or...
talk to the dead.
But until I am presented
with irrefutable proof...
- I will continue to expose
these men and women
for the swindlers they are.
Still carry that check
with you, Car?
Oh, yes.
We offer a
not-insubstantial reward
for anyone whose claims
can be verified.
Get a shot on this?
Camera 1. 100 grand.
How many have taken up
the challenge?
- Oh, dozens.
And how many checks
have you signed?
Yet to sacrifice a nickel,
Jack.
Tonight might be the night,
though, folks.
Right?
I do not need
this man's money.
No, I imagine you don't.
Not when there are so many naive
but well-meaning people prepared
to hand over their hard-earned.
- You okay?
Oh. Do you need
a drink of water?
You okay?
I'm alright, thank you.
Hey, um...
Now, Car, explain to us
Mr. Christou's readings, then,
before we went to break.
- What I saw was an admittedly
accomplished performer
digging from a bag of tricks
that goes back
to biblical times.
By my count, Christou flopped
no less than five times
before he hit on the tenuous
Peterson connection.
- It was Peterman.
He-- He's flawless
in hindsight.
Okay, Car, but I observed
nothing untoward
when Mr. Christou appeared
to connect
these two ladies
with their deceased son.
We all saw that,
everyone here, right?
To which I would say,
even a broken clock
is right twice a day.
False lies!
You no more have the power
of divination
than I resemble Burt Reynolds.
You, sir, like me, are a liar,
a cheat, a charlatan,
and a fake.
The difference being,
I'm honest about it.
Come on.
Oh! Okay.
A flair for the theatrical
doesn't go astray.
Christou, wait, I still
have to ask you something.
Please.
- Christou.
We have not yet discussed
the last reading.
Yet another cold trail.
Minnie, Molly, Mandy, anyone?
Put a sock in it, will you,
Car?
Enough.
Funny as it may seem...
I actually believe
that that last reading
may have been meant for me.
Yes?
Minnie--
Who-- Who's Minnie?
Minnie is the
private nickname
for...
Madeleine, my wife.
- Hmm.
- Your wife?
Yes. S-She crossed over,
didn't she?
An unmarried man
wearing a wedding ring?
I think you meant this.
Jack, please.
Half the people in this room
are wearing one.
- Okay.
- And Madeleine's death
was hardly a secret.
This is what I'm talking about.
It is a statistical certainty
that some fool
will take the bait.
Don't be that fool.
- What are you up to, Car?
- Let's see if the mad monk
really can conjure up
the spirit of your dead wife
live on air.
Half a $1 million
should be incentive enough.
No?
Christou.
Buddy?
- God damn it, man!
Go to a commercial!
Go to a goddamn commercial!
- Clear!
- It's okay.
- Can we get some help here?
It's gonna be okay.
You're just overtired, baby.
No! Something's not right!
We need a doctor!
Get him
to his dressing room now.
And someone just clean up
all this mess.
The Surgeon General
strongly advises
taking Pepto Bismol
before speaking with the dead.
Uh, so, is anyone here
from out of town?
This was a gift
from Charles Laughton,
I'll have you know.
You, you, you.
Fetch the burgundy blazer
from my portmanteau, will you?
Christ, it must have been
a seizure or something.
You play the aw-shucks
Midwesterner so well, Jack.
That bit about Madeleine
and your secret nickname?
Very impressive.
What are you talking about?
There are only three ways
he could have known about that.
One, he's actually psychic,
which we both know
is impossible.
Two, he got lucky. Possible,
but highly improbable.
Or three...
You think that I told him?
I wouldn't blame you
if you did.
A little on-air drama
can't be bad for ratings, right?
- Right, right.
- I do read the trades, Jack.
I'd have thought
your high-powered friends
at The Grove
could pull a few strings.
I think you overestimate
their influence.
You must invite me along
one of these days.
I'd love to know
if the rumors are true--
the secret handshakes,
the orgies,
the arcane ceremonies.
But mostly the orgies.
Jack, rundown briefing.
Give me an audience
with the Grand Poobah, Jack.
I'll fit right in.
Good man, Sticks.
I told you not to leave me
alone with that asshole.
What am I-- your mother?
The ambulance is coming.
You can talk to Cavendish
in the next break.
Extenuating circumstances.
- Any word from Bedford yet?
- Mnh-mnh.
The switchboard lit up
like a Rosenberg, though.
- People are upset? Offended?
- Angry, confused.
None of which is terrible news,
of course. That's great.
- Mr. Fiske.
- No, no, no, no, no.
This comes out
in the next break.
Check your rundown.
Staging, the door.
Shit. Back to the wings.
Oh!
I'm not picking up
anything down here, Steve.
You picking up anything weird,
Lou?
We're on in five...
- Coming through.
...four...
Oh. Not my chair.
Thank you.
And thank you to everyone
who's been calling in
to check on Mr. Christou.
Don't be alarmed, folks.
He is receiving medical
attention backstage as we speak.
They needn't bother.
The man is perfectly fine,
I assure you.
Well... your dry cleaner
may disagree, Car.
Well, that's just an old
vaudeville routine.
Spouting, they call it.
Controlled regurgitation.
Anyway, I certainly hope
you're gonna keep
that check handy.
The check--
- Your breast pocket.
Hmm?
Silky as ever, Car.
He got you, Jack.
My sixth sense
is telling me we may
just see this check again
before the night is through.
I very much doubt that.
Wait until you meet
our next guests.
Giddy with excitement, Jack.
You should be.
Now, about a--
About a month ago,
a manuscript happened
to cross my desk that, well...
I haven't been able to stop
thinking about, quite frankly.
The book...
..."Conversations
with the Devil"
by Dr. June Ross-Mitchell...
...hits shelves this week,
and it is certain
to challenge more than
a few skeptics out there.
Now, before I bring on
the doctor
and the young subject
of the book,
I wanted to share with
you all a clip produced
by June's psi-research center.
Hopefully catch us
all up to speed.
But please be warned, anyone
with young children
in the room--
What you're about to see
is profoundly disturbing
and shocking.
Can we roll the tape, please?
A seemingly ordinary house
on an ordinary street.
Only this is the headquarters
of the infamous
First Church of Abraxas.
I command thee
to come forth
and bestow
these blessings of hell upon us.
Hail, Abraxas!
- Hail, Abraxas!
The church's founder
and leader,
the enigmatic Szandor D'Abo.
Abraxas shows us
there is no good, no evil,
no redemption.
Only what we desire
and how we obtain it.
You make it sound very easy,
Monsieur D'Abo.
Make no mistake--
The master demands sacrifice.
D'Abo's activities come
to the attention of the FBI,
who suspect the cult of
kidnapping and firearm offenses.
But even more alarming
are the stories of children
being bred for human sacrifice.
...and the spilling of blood.
Come forth.
Open the gates of hell.
D'Abo claims that anyone who
witnesses these dreadful rituals
will fall under the spell
of the demon Abraxas,
and so perform
his earthly bidding.
And so it is done!
- Events take a tragic turn
in August '74...
...when federal agencies
lay siege to the house.
Shots have been fired.
After
a tense three-day standoff,
D'Abo commands his followers
to douse the premises
and themselves in gasoline.
But remarkably,
among the smoldering ruins,
a terrified 10-year-old girl
is discovered.
She goes only
by the name of Lilly.
Her memories of her time
in the house--
fractured and incomplete.
Was her survival part
of D'Abo's wicked master plan,
or was she simply
the lucky one?
At a loss to explain Lilly's
strange behavior,
the FBI contacts
my psi research center.
Lilly and I make
an immediate connection.
Important breakthroughs follow,
but there is still
much work to be done.
It's 2:30 p.m.,
July 10, 1976.
This is a recording
of our first session.
Okay.
It seems
we've made contact.
Who am I speaking to now?
Is this the demon known as--
Oh, my God!
Hold her tight!
Help!
We need some help in here!
Wow.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome
Dr. June Ross-Mitchell
and Lilly.
Oh. You can come out.
Hi.
Lilly.
June.
How are ya?
Whoa!
Good to meet ya.
So good to see you again, June.
- You too, Jack.
- And, Lilly
so pleased that you could
join us today.
Thank you, Mr. Delroy.
I'm so glad
you could join us, too.
Now, Lilly, you don't have
to look at the camera.
You can actually
talk directly to me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't be silly.
I want to start with a tough
question, if that's okay.
I'd like to know--
Have you ever watched
my show before?
No.
I'm normally in bed by now.
But I know who you are,
Mr. Delroy.
Oh, please.
You can call me Jack.
June says you're
very handsome, Jack.
You're the man
whose wife died of cancer.
Lilly, I don't think
Jack wants to--
I was very sad
when I heard about that.
I know what it's like to lose
people who are close to you.
It's lonely at first,
but you'll get through.
Such wise words
from one so young, huh?
Lilly has been through more
in her 13 years
than most adults
go through in a lifetime.
And you needn't worry
about your TV show.
I think you're gonna be
very famous soon.
Why, thank you
for the reassurance.
I was beginning to wonder,
Gus.
- Me too.
You're welcome.
Okay, well, we're gonna
take a break.
Um, but on the other side--
yes, the other side--
we're going to spend some time
getting to know
these two extraordinary ladies.
- Okay. That was great.
- Quite a show.
I was afraid
you weren't gonna make it.
I'm sorry.
And we're clear.
Great.
That was great, ladies.
Lilly, you are adorable.
Thank you, Jack.
And which camera
do I look at now?
Um, well, we're off air,
so none.
Time to make ourselves
pretty again.
Hey, Jack.
Don't I already look pretty,
Jack?
You're good.
Sure, you do.
Hi! I'm Lilly!
- Jack, we need to talk.
- Let me take that
for you, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- Wow. Weird kid.
- She was looking
right down that camera.
That was great.
You ready?
- This is so much fun.
Welcome
to the dream factory, kid.
I really don't think
it's a good idea, Jack.
She's becoming
more unpredictable.
See, unpredictable--
That's a good thing.
That's why we still do live TV.
I mean, it's what's
gonna help sell your book.
- This isn't about the book.
- Isn't it?
Yesterday she went into
one of her fugue states,
and she, uh...
she started saying your name.
She's excited about
being on the show.
No, it was as if she was
recalling something.
It was hard to make sense of it,
but it was strange even for her.
Look, you are
ready for this.
You told me that you're ready
for it. You know you did.
Yes. Well, there may have been
a few lapses of judgment
on my part that...
This is your time.
You've done the work.
You're not gonna
back out right now.
Yeah, I admit you made
a convincing case.
But my first responsibility
is to Lilly.
And I'm telling you,
it's too risky.
- No, I--
I should get back to her.
She's not getting cold feet,
is she?
- She's fine. She is fine.
I'm handling it!
- Hey, Jack.
- Hey.
Okay, so just got
a call from Sinai.
Yeah, I know, I know,
I know.
- Christou is dead.
- What?
He had some kind of hemorrhage
in the ambulance.
- Holy shit.
- I know.
No. No, no, no.
I thought that that was
all part of his act.
The-- What did Haig call it?
Spouting?
Well, apparently he was
spouting from, well, everywhere.
The paramedics couldn't
get it under control.
- Jesus Christ!
- I know. I know, I know, I know.
I know, I know, I know.
- Listen to me.
Nobody can find out about this,
especially not Gus.
I'll do the best that I can,
gut you know how quickly
word spreads around here.
- Staging,
where's my sacrificial dagger?
We're on 60 second.
Hey, hey, Phil.
Has the rundown changed?
Staging's saying something
about a new bit in seg five,
and I don't see it on my--
- Wait. Shh, shh, shh.
Look, I'm telling you, Steve,
whatever it is,
we're not seeing it
on the monitor down here.
- Hey, Phil.
- Come on, guys!
You just
keep switching cameras,
and I'll make sure everybody
gets their cues, okay?
- Phil! Phil!
- Stand by, everyone.
- Phil!
- Then there was a questionnaire
you had to complete
before coming in, you say?
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, and there was a lady
in the lobby
who asked a bunch
of questions, too.
Oh, yeah.
It was the same woman
who came out and helped
Mr. Christou when he...
Oh, yes, I know.
Most disturbing, wasn't it?
Thank you, ladies.
- All sorts of stuff lately.
- Yeah.
- No wonder we...
Thank you.
Phil said we're coming back.
Is everything okay, Jack?
Yeah.
Everything is fine, sweetie.
- 10 seconds!
- Where the hell is Haig?
- And we're back in five...
four...
And welcome back
to our very special
Halloween edition
of "Night Owls."
Now, ladies, there is so much
that I'd like
to discuss with you both,
but I want to start
with you, June.
Now, you call yourself
a parapsychologist.
What exactly does that--
- I call myself one
because that's
what I am, Jack.
It so happens
I have a PhD in the subject.
From the University of
Hogwash, if I'm not mistaken.
The Stanford Research
Institute, actually.
The difference being?
Is it really worth us
continuing if this man
is going to interrupt
every time you ask a question?
Car, please behave.
As I was going to say,
we parapsychologists believe
there are certain phenomena,
psi phenomena,
that traditional science
is ill-equipped to understand.
Telepathy, for example.
Telekinesis,
apparitional anomalies.
- Demonic possession.
"Psychic infestation"
is the term we prefer, but yes.
And it's your belief
that Lilly here presents
just such a case.
For the past three years,
I've been combining
age regression therapy
with a growing understanding
of ancient Satanic rituals
to piece together
the details of Lilly's life
and to grasp the nature of
the demon that lurks within her.
This is the demon Abraxas
that the charming Mr. D'Abo
spoke of in your clips?
No, I believe it's more
likely one of the minor deities
said to serve Abraxas.
These entities thrive
on our confusion.
And our stupidity.
Look, I understand
that some of this
might seem to stretch credulity,
but, remember,
big, new scientific ideas
are always greeted
with some resistance.
It's only the most close-minded
that greet them with ridicule.
Incidentally, we have
some pieces here
from your private collection.
- Whew!
Okay, well, girl's
got to have a hobby, huh?
That dagger was recovered
from the remains
of the D'Abo house.
We believe it was used in many
of the church's
sacrificial ceremonies.
No!
Oh, God!
- No! Don't do it!
- I can't stop it!
- Stop!
Turn off your TV sets before
Abraxas claims your souls!
Car?
You truly are a suggestible lot.
Handy to know.
- Mr. Haig,
we haven't come on here
for your amusement.
Don't be silly, my dear.
If we accept
the Gnostic interpretation,
Abraxas is the consummate
showman. He craves an audience.
After all,
his name is the source
of the magician's
favorite incantation.
Abracadabra.
Clever girl.
Now, Lilly, I understand
that you have a name
for this thing
that lives inside of you.
Mm-hmm.
I call him Mr. Wriggles.
And why do you call him that?
He kind of wriggles his way
inside my head,
and then
he wriggles his way out.
But with June's help,
you are able to control him.
June says that everyone
has a demon inside them.
But we can't always
control them, can we?
Gus.
Your timing is...
I got it, Jack.
It's just a matter of...
Ooh!
- Gus!
Is there off switch
for that thing?
How the hell should I know?!
It was feeding back
through your P.A. system.
- No.
- It's the same physics
as when a soprano
hits "G" over high "C."
Poof!
Okay, Car, but come on.
That was--
He's wrong, you know?
It was Mr. Wriggles.
- Mr. Wriggles?!
- He did it.
If you insist, little one.
Why must you be
so condescending, Mr. Haig?
- Lilly, do you mean
that Mr. Wriggles is here
in the studio with us right now?
Mm-hmm.
Would it be okay if we
invited him on the show?
Jack, I thought
I made it clear...
- I think so.
- No, I can't allow that.
A summoning requires a carefully
controlled environment.
The lights, cameras,
audience--
Conditions here
are hardly conducive.
A TV studio's a controlled
enough environment for my money.
Half a million bucks,
to be precise.
Can we? June, please!
- Yeah!
- We want to see!
- Come on, June.
We want to see.
- Do it!
Come on!
- We want to see!
- Show us, June.
Come on, June!
The people have spoken.
If I'm able to conduct
the session
with the full cooperation
of your crew, your audience,
and your guests,
then perhaps we can attempt
a brief demonstration.
- Yeah!
- Yes, of course.
This is great news.
It's great news.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please stay tuned
for a live television first
as we attempt to commune
with the devil.
But not before
a word from our sponsors.
Clear!
Step lively, people.
We have two minutes
to prep the main stage,
checks on June and Lilly.
You bastard.
You ambushed me.
You didn't require
too much convincing, dearie.
Bread and circuses.
- You shut up.
This is your chance
to prove people like him wrong.
This is your moment, June.
Did you hear anything
I said back there?
You know, for a talk show host,
you're a terrible listener.
Is somebody gonna
clean up the glass?
Lilly's okay with it.
Aren't you, sweetheart?
- Sure, Jack.
- Can I get you two ladies
to follow me downstage, please?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- Jack, can I get a minute?
- Can it wait?
No, sir. It cannot.
Excuse me, uh, Phil.
There are
some restraints backstage.
Would you mind?
- Sure.
I hope you know
what you're doing, lady.
We know what we're doing,
Sammy. Don't we, June?
Jerry, you got
the new lighting cues?
What?
You're meddling with things
you don't understand.
Okay. If we...
manage to conjure Satan,
I give you express permission
to go right for that exit.
Okay? If Earth swallows us
whole, I apologize in advance.
Okay?
- What has gotten into you?
Half an hour ago, you thought
Madeleine was trying to reach
out to you from the grave.
And now...
- Now-- Now, buddy,
all I'm trying to do is save
our fucking show. Okay?
So enough
with the sanctimonious crap.
I know about Christou.
It's that Mr. Wriggles,
isn't it?
He's behind this whole thing.
Who else knows
about Christou?
Crew's scared, Jack.
I'm scared.
Okay? Some of us
are talking about jumping ship.
No one's going anywhere,
God damn it.
And you need to keep this
fire-and-brimstone bullshit
to yourself.
Please, Gus?
Okay?
- You are not a bad man, Jack.
You're not.
And I am begging you
to stop this before
something terrible happens.
Jack, you're gonna intro
the girls downstage.
Mm.
Is there a problem here?
Stand by, everybody.
There's no problem.
We are back in five...
four...
Welcome back, everyone.
Without further ado,
Dr. June Ross-Mitchell
will commence
the demonstration.
And might I say to you both,
Godspeed?
Thank you, Jack.
Now, if the entity
is present tonight,
it may manifest itself
in any number of ways,
but its entry into our world
is only possible through Lilly.
I merely provide the key
that unlocks the door.
Whatever you might see or hear,
I ask you all to remain calm.
It's vital that Lilly's
focus remains with me.
Let us begin.
Lilly, to me.
Close your eyes, Lilly.
That's it.
And let yourself sleep.
Relax.
Lilly, can you hear me?
Lilly?
May I speak to the one
you know as Mr. Wriggles?
If Mr. Wrig--
Quiet.
May I ask who is present now?
Shh!
Please let yourself be known.
Speak.
You know who I am, Doctor.
Please.
- Is that the devil?
- I'm so scared.
Is she okay?
Who are
these people?
What is this?
Where am I?!
- There is no need to be alarmed.
What have you done to me,
Doctor?
We mean you no harm.
We've brought you into
this realm to better understand
your purpose.
My purpose?
He's here, isn't he?
Good to see you again, Jack.
Nah. Sorry.
I don't believe
we've been acquainted.
Don't be a fool.
We go way back.
We met amongst the tall trees.
Remember?
- Lilly, return to me.
Oh, Juney, Juney, Juney, Juney!
Be careful now.
You know what happened
to his last whore.
She died.
She died an ugly, ugly death.
Lilly, come back to me-- now!
And the worms finished off
with Minnie a long time ago,
didn't they, Jack?
So now you can screw up whoever
you want, hmm? Like Dr. June.
Dr. June thinks you're
very handsome, Jack.
Dr. June thinks
you're very, very handsome.
That's enough! Lilly, I need
you to come back to me now!
Jack and June went up the hill
to fuck each other's brains out.
Jack and Jill went up the hill
to [bleep] each other's--
That's enough!
Lilly?
Lilly, sweetheart?
Why would
you hurt me like that, June?
You know I can't help it.
I know. I never--
No, Jack! Stay where you are.
Vade retro Satana.
Sunt mala quae libas.
You were cursed by Anum
and Antum, Lahmum and Du-rum,
The Underworld
and those who lie in it,
that you shall not seize her,
and you shall not return.
- And you shall not return!!
How could you let it happen,
Jack?
How could you let it happen?
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no. No, I'm sorry.
I never should have put you
in that position. Okay?
You're okay. You're okay.
Just breathe.
That was...
You're okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
have you ever seen anything
like that?
This is unconscionable, Jack.
I would like to point out
a number of tricks employed
by the so-called doctor.
And you'll get your turn, Car.
Right now...
some messages.
We're clear.
Is this a talk show
or a fucking freak show?!
I mean, the depths you people
have sunk to.
Carmichael, just take it easy, okay?
Let's get Sammy in
to mop that brow of yours.
Sammy?
Lilly, are you okay?
A bit embarrassed, I guess.
I'm okay.
Phil. I'm sorry. Can we get
a hand with these straps?
- I got you.
- June.
Come here. Come here.
Just, let's...
You're okay.
Jesus.
That was-- I mean...
I knew that we were gonna see
something amazing tonight,
but...
we got to get you guys
back on as soon as possible.
This could become,
like, a regular spot.
The tall trees.
What did she mean by that?
I don't know.
You tell me.
This isn't some kind
of parlor trick, Jack.
I know that, June.
I mean, this...
There is something very special
happening here with Lilly.
With you.
I just-- I want
to be a part of it.
- Uh! You're hurting me!
- Sorry, kid.
Look, I'm trying here.
- Hey, Phil.
It's okay, it's okay.
I got this.
Can I see that? Thanks.
Thanks, guys.
Go ahead.
It's okay, Lilly. It's okay.
- Thank you, Jack.
- Mm-hmm.
No, she's great.
She's got it all.
Well, this is all very exciting.
Thank you so much.
- Sorry.
- Send regards to Bonnie
and the kids. Okay. Bye-bye.
- We'll have you back next year.
This isn't about ratings
anymore, Leo. This is sorcery.
Listen to me, you goddamn
shit-your-pants Mick asshole!
Dial up that grin.
Dial it up.
Dial it up
and get on with your job.
And not one more word.
It's all smoke and mirrors,
Gus. Trust me.
Leo should have cut the whole
show right after Christou died.
Bombed, you mean?
No. Didn't you hear?
He's dead.
Puked his guts out
on the way to Sinai.
Two minutes, everyone.
We're on the homestretch.
Let's keep it going.
- Thank you, Jack.
Yeah. Come here.
And what are we
doing now, Jack?
Um, now it's nearly time
to say good night, darling.
Oh.
- Jack.
Sammy.
Checks on June and Lilly.
Okay, so three of the crew
have just walked off,
the Communications Commission
have called an emergency meeting
at 7:00 a.m., and...
- Bedford.
- Mm-hmm.
What did he say?
Just that he thinks
it's the biggest TV event
since the moon landing.
Who was I to disagree?
- We're back!
Baby! Back! We're back
from the fucking dead!
We're talking about 35,
maybe even 40 share.
"The night Jack Delroy
interviewed
that cock-fucking devil"!
- Well, it might not
be the headline The Times,
run with, or The Post,
for that matter,
but something in that vein.
Oh, and Bedford also took
quite a liking
to-- to June, too.
Asked when she'd be back.
- I'll do what I can.
I guess I don't have to
kiss Cavendish's ass.
Cavendish?
Screw Cavendish.
After tonight, every fucking
Fortune 500 will be lining up
to be a part of the resurrection
of Jack Delroy.
If anyone's gonna be
kissing ass, it's them.
What's the matter?
Just
That girl's voice...
I know. How did she do that?
Yeah, but at the end, I mean,
she sounded just like Minnie.
You heard that.
- No, no, no, no.
Don't-- Don't you go
all screwy on me, Jack.
I've already got Gus back there
prepping for an exorcism.
I just got spooked.
That's all.
Let me tell you something.
If Minnie were here,
she'd be saying,
"You get out there,
Mr. Midnight,
and you knock 'em dead."
Positions, people.
10 seconds.
We'll drop the costume parade
to give Carmichael
a few more minutes
on his soapbox,
and then we'll wrap it up,
throw it to Cleo.
10 seconds, people.
- Jack.
- Can we have Cleo standing by?
Dagger.
And in five...
four...
Welcome back.
Ladies and gentlemen,
before we continue,
I'd like to apologize to anyone
who may have been upset
or offended
by what you saw
before the break.
It's not every day that you see
a demonic possession
on live television.
Lilly...
can you assure everyone
that you're okay?
Yes. I'm fine, Jack.
And do you have
any recollection
of what just happened?
It's hard to explain.
It's like I'm asleep,
but I'm awake at the same time.
I just try to focus
on June's voice.
I'm sorry if Mr. Wriggles
said anything rude.
Alright, enough with
all this subterfuge.
May I, Jack?
- Yeah. Oh, please.
Because, you know, I'm dying
to hear you explain away
what we all just witnessed here.
Let's hear it.
Let me preface this by saying
that my chief concern
is the welfare,
indeed the sanity,
of this young girl.
- How dare you?
- I beg your pardon?
Before I became her guardian,
Lilly lived in the cruelest
conditions imaginable.
I studied her, yes.
I treated her.
But I also gave her two things
I'm sure you're just
as skeptical of--
love and compassion.
Lilly and I are family.
I can assure you all
there is no demon
lurking inside this child.
Clearly, she has been placed
in a hypnotic state,
then manipulated
by the good doctor
to perform her bit.
- Hypnosis?
Then-- Then how do you explain
the physical transformations
with her skin?
The voice changed.
There was banging
on the walls of the studio.
- She levitated, for God's sakes!
- Granted,
the stagecraft was impeccable.
- Do you know what I think, Car?
- Pray tell.
I think that you are just
a self-righteous,
coldhearted curmudgeon
who's trying to weasel
his way out of parting
with half a million bucks.
- Yeah!
If you'll allow me, Jack,
I'd like to prove my thesis
beyond a shadow of doubt.
Be my guest.
- I'll need a volunteer.
- Thank you, Gus.
- Hmm?
Yes, if you'll join me
center stage.
Could I have those chairs
back here, please?
Do as you're told, Gus.
Gus.
Car. You've got five minutes.
Make 'em count.
Don't worry, Jack.
What I have in store
should provide a very fitting
climax to your show.
My wife likes the way
my head sits on my shoulders,
Mr. Haig.
I hope you're not
planning to, uh...
Make it spin?
Oh, I plan to make
everybody's head spin.
Could I just have the lights
dimmed, please?
A bit of atmosphere never hurt,
did it, Dr. June?
You know what we say
in TV land--
Where there's smoke, there's
probably a smoke machine.
My compliments to the producer.
Okay, Gus.
Are we feeling comfortable?
Sure.
I hope everyone here
in the studio
and you at home are
all feeling comfortable, too.
It's important that everyone
is as relaxed as they can be.
Now, I have something here
that I want you all to look at.
Do you think we might be able
to get a close-up?
Mm.
I will now ask you all
to stare into my watch.
Even you, Jack.
Got a good shot
on all the studio monitors here.
I hope our viewers at home
are also paying attention.
Watch carefully.
'Round...
and 'round, it goes.
Is everyone feeling
nice and relaxed?
Good.
Now, Gus...
- Hmm?
...tell me all about
this vermiphobia of yours.
I'm sorry. My what?
Your morbid fear of worms.
How do you know about that?
What is it about them
that so unsettles you?
Isn't it obvious?
They're such ugly, slimy things.
No arms, no legs, no eyes.
Indeed. Quite grotesque.
And they seem to thrive
wherever it's dark and moist--
the soil, the mud,
the human body, even.
Disgusting.
Do you realize that you are now
deep in a trance?
No, sir, I do not.
A very... deep...
trance.
Okey-dokey. You're the expert.
And when I click my fingers,
you will be entirely
under my command.
Look, this is silly.
I don't think it--
Gus, can you hear me?
Yes.
Do you know where you are?
Here...
in the studio with you.
You don't feel any different?
No.
Why should I?
What is that? Do you hear that?
Geez, it's...
It's hot in here.
Skin's itchy.
You alright, Gus?
Yeah.
Just, uh, so damn itchy.
Your neck.
It's bleeding.
I did nick myself shaving
earlier.
Geez.
What is that?
Jesus!
Now, just stay calm, Gus.
No. No! I can feel them.
They're inside me.
Jesus!
Aaaahhh!
Aah!
Oh, God!
Help me, Car.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Why is Gus acting so silly?
This wasn't meant to happen.
Uhh!
Dreamer, here!
Awake!
How do you feel, Gus?
- Fine.
Uh, when do we begin?
- Oh!
- Geez! When did that happen?
Geez.
You mean you have no idea?
There were worms all over you.
Worms?
Oh, God, I hope not.
I hate worms.
Okay, Car.
What the hell just happened?
I did the exact
same thing June did,
just with
a tad more imagination.
You said I used to be the best.
Perhaps I still am.
Now would be
the appropriate time to applaud.
Mm.
You're saying you
just hypnotized all of us?
I'm pretty sure I had
most of you here in the studio,
and no doubt a number
of our viewers at home.
Fortunately,
you're a suggestible lot.
What's he talking about, June?
He played a mean trick on us,
that's all.
Leo, um, can you get the guys
up in videotape
to play back that last bit?
Yep. Lining it up.
Now, if Carmichael's right--
if-- then...
oh, boy. We're in store for
some very interesting viewing.
Bravo. Yes, let's do that.
Best idea you've had
all night, Jack.
They're cueing it up now.
Let's start there.
You don't feel any different?
No.
Why should I?
Because something dreadful
is about to happen.
It's dawning on you.
Hear that?
Ghostly sounds,
anguished moaning from beyond.
That is not the way
I remember it.
You're hot.
You're itchy.
Feels like something's
crawling under your skin.
It's hot in here.
Skin's getting itchy.
Your neck. It's bleeding.
I did cut myself
shaving earlier.
- What?!
- What is that?
- Worms.
Jesus Christ!
That's right. Worms.
Dozens of them.
Hundreds of them.
Now, just stay calm, Gus.
No! They're inside of me.
I can feel 'em!
Show me.
- Get 'em out!
- They are coming out.
Oh, boy.
Okay, let's stop there.
I've never been
so embarrassed in my whole life.
Is there...
anyone who did not see the worms
the first time around?
I didn't see them.
- One.
- I didn't see them.
You did? Okay.
So aside from a couple
of people in the audience,
uh, it looks like you
have made fools of us all
once again, Car.
All in a day's work.
I did not hypnotize Lilly,
or the studio audience,
or the viewers at home.
- Oh, come on, Doctor.
You've been caught
dead to rights.
At least America can sleep
a little easier
knowing the devil's not going to
pop out of their TV screens.
If Mr. Haig thinks we're
playing a trick on everyone,
then maybe we should look back
at that part of the show, too,
Jack.
- Yeah.
Do you mean when
Mr. Wriggles joined us?
Mm-hmm.
You don't think
the television cameras lie,
do you, Mr. Haig?
- No, of course not.
- Jack, please.
Lilly has been through enough.
No.
Okay, folks. I'm sorry.
Our producers are telling me
that the lovely Miss Cleo James
is standing by
to take us out.
And...
I...
I just think maybe we should
bring her back at a later date,
because we can't leave
everybody hanging like this.
- Yeah!
I'm sorry. We can no longer
take any part in any of this.
Lilly, we're leaving.
But we want everyone
to know the truth.
Don't we, June?
- Yeah!
- Standing by, Jack.
- We're staying.
Please.
- We could start it.
Yeah. Right there.
It's gonna be okay.
Speak.
You know who I am, Doctor.
- Quiet.
- You say cameras
don't lie, right, Car?
- Who are these people?
What is this?
There must be
some rational explanation.
My IFSIP team may need
to take these tapes in
for forensic examination.
My purpose?
Good to see you again, Jack.
Sorry. I don't believe
we've been acquainted.
- Don't be a fool.
- Did you see that?
- We go way back.
- I'm sorry. Can you stop it?
Just go back a few seconds.
Stop.
Okay.
Go from there, but very slow, please.
Good to see you again, Jack.
Slower.
Sorry.
I don't believe we've been...
Okay. Freeze it there.
That's just a glitch, Jack.
No, it's something else.
Now go one frame at a time.
No, no. Sl--
Can you slow it down?
Keep going.
Minnie?
My God!
It is you.
You set the whole thing up.
Did you really think
another special appearance
from Madeleine might actually
save your little gabfest?
- You're okay.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This-- This makes
perfect sense.
You-- You conspire
with Christou
to have him reach
your dead wife,
throw in a few Grand Guignol
theatrics with these two,
and then top it all off
with some clever
videotape manipulation.
It's genius, Jack.
Cynical, depraved genius.
Ladies,
the encore is quite unnecessary!
Um...
Can we get some help here?
Now!
Uh! Aah!
Cut the show, Leo!
Cut it!
The power of Christ compels you!
The power of Christ--
Gus!
Lilly, to me!
Aah!
Lord of Flies,
God of Ungodliness,
I solemnly promise to worship
and obey thee
and perform thy unholy bidding.
Oh, fuck.
Abracadabra.
Everybody, get out!
Jack! Jack! Come on!
Come on. Please. Please.
But now here's Mr. Midnight...
Jack Delroy!
- Jack! Jack!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Jack!
Come on in, Jack.
We love you, Jack!
How did I get here?
The same way you always
get here, Jack--
straight down 5th
and right on 47th.
You okay, Jack?
I am sick of it, Crog!
Stuck in the cave all day
cooking your saber-tooth stew
while you
and your troglodyte buddies
go out hunting all day long.
What the fuck is going on?
Don't think that's the line
we rehearsed.
Leo!
Oh, where are you going, Jack?
Jack, we're still on air.
Jack?
Now, I've brought
something really special
for you today, Jack.
Here she is.
I'll just get her out so you
can have a really good look.
Hello!
- Jesus.
- Here she is.
- Relax.
Jack, she's perfectly harmless.
- No.
Jack and I first met
when I was doing "Oh! Calcutta!"
at the Eden.
My, you should have
seen him blush
when he came backstage
and was confronted
with all those
glorious naked bodies.
Remember, darling?
No.
Is that another thing
you've managed to forget?
You're dead.
Okay, Penelope.
Now give the Wheel of Wonder
a big spin.
Just remember to let go.
Last week we had a lady
go 'round for hours and hours.
Spin the wheel!
Switch off your televisions.
Turn off your TV sets.
Stop watching this.
Turn it off!
Stop!
Please.
Aah!
Stop it!
- Welcome to the family, Jack.
- Over here!
Jack, Jack. Congratulations
on your ratings win.
What did you have to sacrifice
to get here tonight?
Oh, Jack Delroy's greatest
sacrifice is yet to come.
Hm.
Great show tonight, Jack.
At least a 40 share.
Maybe even a 50.
Come.
Now drink up, Jack.
There you are.
I was worried they wouldn't
let you see me.
They told you
you could have it all.
Didn't they?
Be number one?
Well, you finally made it, darling.
But you had to pay a price.
Exit Minnie, stage left.
I never thought that they'd...
Your soul belonged to them.
Still does.
It wasn't supposed
to turn out this way.
You have to believe me.
You're on your own now, Jack.
I love you.
I love you, Minnie.
Then, please...
do this one last thing for me.
The pain. Please.
Please.
You know what to do.
- Oh.
Do it. Do it.
Yes.
Dreamer, here. Awake.
Dream, here. Awake.
Dream, here.
♪ Write another song
for the money ♪
♪ Something they can sing,
not so funny ♪
♪ Money in the bank
to keep us warm ♪
♪ Roll another joint
for the Gipper ♪
♪ Get the Gipper high,
he gets hipper ♪
♪ Stick it in his mouth
and keep him warm ♪
♪ Elect another jerk
to the White House ♪
♪ Gracie Slick is losing
her dormouse ♪
♪ Take her off the streets
and keep warm ♪